iTop Screenshot Release Histoy

Release v1.2 - Jun 10, 2021
+ Strengthened the screenshot editing feature by adding Line, Arrow, and Pixelation.
+ Added the function to search similar images on Google.
+ Optimized the update process to get the latest version more conveniently.
+ Improved UI for better user experience.
+ Improved multiple languages for better localization.
+ Fixed known bugs.

Release v1.1 - Apr 27, 2021
+ Added the support for capturing scrolling windows like entire web pages and long documents.
+ Newly supported pinning several screenshots at one time and previewing screenshots and zooming in/out.
+ Newly supported sharing screenshots to Twitter with Ctrl+V.
+ Improved the feature of saving screenshots to the clipboard with Ctrl+C and exiting capture with ESC.
+ Improved multiple languages and added Arabic, German, Romanian, Ukrainian, and Vietnamese.
+ Fixed known bugs.

Release v1.0 - Apr 2, 2021
+ Quickly take screenshots of a selected region, window, or full screen.
+ Easily annotate and highlight screenshots with Rectangle, Oval, Paintbrush, and Text.
+ Save screenshots in various popular image formats like JPEG, PNG, and BMP.
+ Pin screenshots to desktop directly for instant view.
+ Easily share screenshots to Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, and Imgur.
+ Simple and easy-to-use UI with hotkeys.
+ Localization: 27 languages supported.